let MCQS = [
            {
            question: "Which one of the following is the process of inserting an element in the stack?",
    choice1: "Insert",
    choice2: "Add",
    choice3: "Push",
    choice4: "None of the above",
    answer: 2
},
            {
            question: " ___________is the technology that connects the machines and people within a site in a small area.",
    choice1: "LAN",
    choice2: "MAN",
    choice3: "WAN",
    choice4: "None of these",
    answer: 0
},
            {
            question: "Which of the following is not an example of DBMS?",
    choice1: "MySQL",
    choice2: "Microsoft Acess",
    choice3: "IBM DB2",
    choice4: "Google",
    answer: 3
    
},
            {
            question: "The part of the computer that anyone can touch.",
    choice1: "Hardware",
    choice2: "Software",
    choice3: "Data",
    choice4: "Input",
    answer: 0
},
            {
            question: "Who is the father of PHP language?",
    choice1: "Dennis Ritchie",
    choice2: "James Gosling",
    choice3: "Rasmus Lerdorf",
    choice4: "Charles Luce",
    answer: 2
},
            {
            question: "What type of CSS is generally recommended for designing large web pages?",
    choice1: "Inline",
    choice2: "Internal",
    choice3: "External",
    choice4: "None of the above",
    answer: 2
},
            {
               question: "Which of the following is not a valid C variable name?",
    choice1: "int number;",
    choice2: "float rate;",
    choice3: "int variable_count;",
    choice4: "int $main;",
    answer: 3
},{
               question: "All keywords in C are in ___  ",
    choice1: "LowerCase letters",
    choice2: "UpperCase letters",
    choice3: "CamelCase letters",
    choice4: "None of the mentioned",
    answer: 0
},
            {
               question: "If the Area of Circle is 154 cm2 , then its perimeter  is",
    choice1: "11 cm",
    choice2: "44 cm",
    choice3: "22 cm",
    choice4: "55 cm",
    answer: 1
},
            {
               question: "Which of the following methods is used to access HTML element in javascript?",
    choice1: "getElementById()",
    choice2: "getElementByClassName()",
    choice3: "Both A and B",
    choice4: "None of the above",
    answer: 2
}];